<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"> <id>/</id><title>Joint Warfare</title><subtitle>Daily and weekly posts about living with Arthritis, while building strength and improving mobility.</subtitle> <updated>2022-08-13T15:53:45+00:00</updated> <author> <name>Kevin Bergin</name> <uri>/</uri> </author><link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml"/><link rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" href="/"/> <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.2">Jekyll</generator> <rights> © 2022 Kevin Bergin </rights> <icon>/assets/img/favicons/favicon.ico</icon> <logo>/assets/img/favicons/favicon-96x96.png</logo> <entry><title>Day 20</title><link href="/posts/day-0020/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 20" /><published>2022-08-13T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-08-13T14:06:40+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/day-0020/</id> <content src="/posts/day-0020/" /> <author> <name>Kevin Bergin</name> </author> <category term="daily" /> <summary> It’s so hot. 30 god damn degrees. In Ireland. Very nice to look at though. And still lovely walking weather if you get out early enough. Wrapped up the week with a short kettlebell work out. Don’t want to lose my KB focus while training with barbells. Annoyingly, I tweaked my neck pressing the 32. Feel silly now. I was tired, didn’t sleep great because of the heat, had a few beers last night... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Day 19</title><link href="/posts/day-0019/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 19" /><published>2022-08-12T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-08-13T13:55:53+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/day-0019/</id> <content src="/posts/day-0019/" /> <author> <name>Kevin Bergin</name> </author> <category term="daily" /> <summary> Another lovely morning. Went for a medium length walk (around 35 mins). It’s such a shame that the paths are empty at this time. I think a lot of people would really enjoy it if they got out early for a walk on beautiful day (provided they have that luxury). Push day in the gym today. Didn’t go too heavy - I think bench presses are my weakest movement. Much prefer overhead. Met up with some ... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Day 18</title><link href="/posts/day-0018/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 18" /><published>2022-08-11T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-08-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/day-0018/</id> <content src="/posts/day-0018/" /> <author> <name>Kevin Bergin</name> </author> <category term="daily" /> <summary> Yet another amazing morning. The heat is pretty brutal during the day, needed to just take a cold shower at one point (I’m being dramatic, it’s only 25C, but I’m not used to it). But in the morning, when it’s fresh and bright - kind of hard to be beat just being outside in that. Woke up early today again, was rough sleeping in the heat - even with the chilli pad. Also found that my back was at... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Day 17</title><link href="/posts/day-0017/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 17" /><published>2022-08-10T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-08-10T21:25:57+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/day-0017/</id> <content src="/posts/day-0017/" /> <author> <name>Kevin Bergin</name> </author> <category term="daily" /> <summary> Another amazing morning for a walk. I feel like I need to keep saying it. To be grateful while it lasts. Went for a longer walk than I usually do in the morning, around 40 minutes instead of 20. It was deadlift day at B2B. I’ve never really deadlifted before, and naturally I’m a bit concerned about my back. It went well though. Happy enough with the weight and my hamstring / glutes are burni... </summary> </entry> <entry><title>Day 16</title><link href="/posts/day-0016/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Day 16" /><published>2022-08-09T00:00:00+00:00</published> <updated>2022-08-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated> <id>/posts/day-0016/</id> <content src="/posts/day-0016/" /> <author> <name>Kevin Bergin</name> </author> <category term="daily" /> <summary> Waking up in Ireland lately has been like waking up in Gran Canaria. Blue skies, warm air and sun shining all day. Really being spoiled with walking conditions - gonna miss it when it’s gone. That morning sunshine on my skin seems like it’s really great for both mood and morning wakefulness. Feeling quite a lot of DOMS today! Changing up the workout (KB to barbell squats, and a lot more volum... </summary> </entry> </feed>
